Sometimes you need a girl, to get the girl.
Just Go with It is a comedy, romance film directed by Dennis Dugan.
While romancing Palmer, a much younger schoolteacher, plastic surgeon Danny Maccabee enlists his loyal
assistant Katherine to pretend to be his soon to be ex-wife, in order to cover up a careless lie.
When more lies backfire, Katherine's kids become involved, and everyone heads
off for a weekend in Hawaii that will change all their lives.
Danny Maccabee, played by Adam Sandler.
Katherine Murphy, played by Jennifer Aniston.
Palmer Dodge, played by Brooklyn Decker.
Devlin Adams, played by Nicole Kidman.
Eddie Simms, played by Nick Swardson.
Maggie Murphy, played by Bailee Madison.
Just Go with It is a 2011 American romantic comedy film directed by Dennis Dugan, written by Allan Loeb
and Timothy Dowling, and produced by Adam Sandler, Jack Giarraputo, and Heather Parry.
It is a loose remake of the 1969 film Cactus Flower,
and stars Sandler and Jennifer Aniston.
It tells the story of a plastic surgeon who enlists his
assistant to help him woo a sixth-grade math teacher.
Production of the film began on March 2, 2010.
Originally titled Holiday in Hawaii and then Pretend Wife, it was produced by Sandler's Happy Madison
Productions and released in North America on February 11, 2011, by Columbia Pictures.
The film grossed over $214 million, becoming a box-office success.
It received negative reviews with criticism for the plot and
editing, but some praise for its acting and writing.
Just Go with It won two Golden Raspberry Awards for Worst
Actor (Sandler) and Worst Director (Dugan).
The film explores themes of friendship, hawaii,
assistant, plastic surgery, romcom.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.